submityourarticle.com 2018-12-29

# SubmitYourArticle.com - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy statement relates to SubmitYourArticle.com, owned by Takanomi Limited.

Takanomi Limited is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998, Registration Number Z9318878.

In this policy, where used, _You_ and _Your_ refers to the visitor to this website or Customer of Takanomi Limited; _website_ refers to SubmitYourArticle.com and its subdomains; _Customer_ , _Agreement_ and _Service_ are afforded the same meaning as defined in our Terms and Conditions document.

For each visitor to this website, our web server automatically recognizes the visitors IP address, but not the email address.

We collect the IP address, the email addresses of those who communicate with us or subscribe to receive information via email, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the visitor, and information related to any purchase(s) made by the visitor.

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

We use cookies to record session information, past activity, information relating to a third party (affiliate) via whom the visitor may have accessed the site, and for tracking and remarketing (including Google Adwords remarketing) purposes. You have the right to refuse cookies, and to delete any cookies that may have already been set. Full information on how you can do this can be found at <http://www.aboutcookies.org/>.

Remarketing may be used to display suitable advertisements to visitors after they have visited this website, on other websites they visit subsequently. Visitors and their actions are also tracked using Google Analytics, including conversion tracking functionality provided through Google Adwords.

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by contacting us.

If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive information for which you provided us your address, and may receive other marketing materials to related products or services we believe you may find of interest.

Persons who supply us with their telephone number may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online, or other information they may have requested, or information regarding related products or services we believe you may find of interest.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about them.

Visitors can access this information, and have this information corrected, by contacting us.

The information we collect is stored and used for internal review and marketing purposes, and is not shared with other organisations for commercial purposes.

Unless it is required to do so by law, or where required as part of a sale of, or part of, the business controlled by Takanomi Limited, Takanomi Limited will not provide any personal data we have collected to third parties other than its employees, affiliates or contractors to the extent required in the day to day running of the business and the service provided to customers.

To perform its obligations under the Agreement, Takanomi Limited shall collect personal information, such as, but not limited to: (i) the Customer name, including first and last names, and any title as appropriate, (ii) address, (iii) phone number, (iv) email address, (v) their IP address for determining the Customer geo-location, that is not otherwise publicly available.

Takanomi Limited will keep the personal data provided by the Customer as long as required in order to perform their obligations under the Agreement, and their legal and proper accounting obligations.

The Customer recognizes that they are the controller of all personal data given to Takanomi Limited to process. Takanomi Limited shall be responsible for ensuring sufficient security measures for the processing of personal data provided by the Customer.

Visitors to this website, including the Customer, shall have sole responsibility for any and all information used and submitted in connection with the Service or other use of this website. Takanomi Limited shall have no responsibility thereto. You shall comply with all data protection and privacy laws and rules applicable to information from or regarding third parties. You shall defend, indemnify, and hold Takanomi Limited harmless from any claim, suit or proceeding brought against Takanomi Limited by third parties in connection with any acts or omissions with regards to such information.

The Customer may refer their clients to this Privacy Policy.

You agree and acknowledge that your information collected through the Service or in connection with the Service or as part of other usage of this website may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world in which Takanomi Limited maintains servers, offices, service providers, or has employees or contractors, including the United States.

When you write to us with positive comments on our service, we may use such comments as and where appropriate within our marketing materials and you agree to such usage. Where used, such comments will be attributed to you using only your name and geographical area (eg. state and country), and on request your domain name or website. Your privacy is fully respected and we will not use or publish such comments where they contain sensitive business information without requesting permission in writing from you first. Comments may be edited on occasion in order to clarify meaning, assist readability, and maintain consistent editorial standards.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any point without prior notice. You are advised to check this privacy policy at regular intervals to ensure your continuing agreement. By using this website you signify your agreement with this privacy policy.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, or if you have any comments you wish to make, you are welcome to contact us.
